<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Ando Demian</title><description>If you can&apos;t do Good, better do Bad well.</description><link>https://andodemian.com/</link><item><title>How I Taught My Thermostat to Follow the Sun</title><link>https://andodemian.com/posts/how-i-taught-my-thermostat-to-follow-the-sun/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://andodemian.com/posts/how-i-taught-my-thermostat-to-follow-the-sun/</guid><description>A story about how I automated my home heating with Home Assistant to react dynamically to solar power production, turning excess sunlight into comfort, not wasted watts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astro - Github Actions and Github Pages</title><link>https://andodemian.com/posts/astro-github-actions-pages/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://andodemian.com/posts/astro-github-actions-pages/</guid><description>Dive into this concise guide on deploying Astro sites to GitHub Pages using GitHub Actions. Discover the joy of juggling configuration files and the thrill of automating deployments. By the end, you&apos;ll either have a sleek website up and running, or a newfound appreciation for the simpler things in life – like static HTML.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 22:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFS v3 vs v4.2 - Nothing to write home about</title><link>https://andodemian.com/posts/nfs-v3-vs-v42/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://andodemian.com/posts/nfs-v3-vs-v42/</guid><description>This post offers a direct comparison between NFS v3 and NFS v4.2, focusing on their practical differences and applications. It covers the basic functionalities of NFS v3, known for its simplicity and reliability, and contrasts them with the advanced features of NFS v4.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 21:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Find - Why so slow</title><link>https://andodemian.com/posts/find-why-so-slow/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://andodemian.com/posts/find-why-so-slow/</guid><description>Cut through the clutter in Linux file searching. This post dives into the &apos;find&apos; command, showing you why starting closer to your target beats searching from the root, and how &apos;maxdepth&apos; is your real ally in the file jungle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 12:56:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>